ultimate-codecs.com 2012-09-20

# Tweaks - Free software

## PRIVACY POLICY

Tweaks and its affiliates, collectively "Tweaks", are committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy statement explains data collection and use practices of the Tweaks website and products. We are providing you with this policy to inform you the terms and conditions of the collection of any information.

#### Collection of personal information

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you, e.g. when subscribing to our e-mail newsletter, other opt-in communications, or when purchasing, downloading and/or registering Tweaks products. The information we collect may include information that identifies you including your name, company or organization name, e-mail, phone, work or home address, and credit card information. When you visit our web site we gather certain general information about your visit, such as the IP address through which you access the Internet; the pages that you access while at the Site; the date and time you access the Site and the IP address of the web site which brought you to our site. This information is used to help improve our services, analyze trends, and administer the Site.

#### Collection of non-personal information

When you open an HTML email message from us or install a third party application offered by us during installation of one of our products, we automatically record certain data using technology, including cookies and IP addresses. This data includes the email message you opened and the third party application you installed. This data helps us evaluate the effectiveness of our email and advertising campaigns. The stored Automatically Collected Information does not contain any information that can personally identify you or any of our users. We also track user traffic patterns from standard web server log files. We store statistics about domain names, browser types and IP addresses.

#### Use of personal information

The personal information collected on our Site will be used to operate Tweaks and to provide the service(s) or carry out the transaction(s) you have requested or authorized. We may use your personal information to provide you with important information about the product(s) that you are using, including critical updates and notifications. When you sign up for our newsletter, we may use customized links or similar technologies to track e-mail links that you click. We may associate that information with your personal information in order to provide you more focused e-mail communications or purchase information. We may disclose your Personal Identifying Information to third parties if we are required to do so by law, or if we believe that such action is necessary to: Protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our web site and/or Tweaks products. Comply with legal processes such as a search warrant, subpoena, or court order; Protect our rights and property We never loan, rent or sell your Personal Identifying Information to others. Except as otherwise described in this statement, personal information you provide on the Sites will not be shared outside of Tweaks without your permission.

#### Use of Cookies

We may set and access cookies on your computer. Cookies are small text files that most web sites, including Tweaks, place on your computer. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Most web browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can modify your browser setting to accept or decline cookies. Some of our web pages may require that you accept cookies. If you decide or set your browser not to accept cookies you will not be able to access those web pages. For information on how to disable cookies you should consult the instructions that accompanied your web browser.

#### Minors

No information may be submitted to Tweaks via the Site by persons, who are minors under their applicable local legislation. In the event you are a minor or younger than legal age in your country, you will need consent from your parent(s) or other legal guardian(s) before submitting any information to Tweaks via the Site, with the exception if such activities are allowed by applicable law of your country. We look forward hearing from you: support@tweaks-soft.com
